{
    "subject": "Jesse_Birdsall",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Gwyneth_Strong",
    "human_readable": "Jesse Birdsall is married to Gwyneth Strong.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9748008847236633,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Jesse Birdsall and Gwyneth Strong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.913467526435852,
            "question": "Name the person Gwyneth Strong is married to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9072368741035461,
            "question": "Who is Jesse Birdsall married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8726588487625122,
            "question": "Who is married to Gwyneth Strong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.813470184803009,
            "question": "Is Jesse Birdsall's marital status 'married'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8100959062576294,
            "question": "To whom is Jesse Birdsall legally bound in marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7413309812545776,
            "question": "Is Jesse Birdsall in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6753173470497131,
            "question": "What is the name of Gwyneth Strong's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4742595851421356,
            "question": "What is the name of Gwyneth Strong's partner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04307663440704346,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in a marital union according to the provided information?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jesse Birdsall is married to Gwyneth Strong.",
            "html": "yago_5639_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Gwyneth Strong's partner?",
            "html": "yago_5639_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Gwyneth Strong's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_5639_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jesse Birdsall in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_5639_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5639_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Jesse Birdsall and Gwyneth Strong were married in the year 2000."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Jesse Birdsall and Gwyneth Strong have been married since July 15, 2000, confirming the marital relationship between them."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}